Guide to the Records of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2002
Library of Virginia
- Series XX. Scheduling Office: Reading files, 1997-2002 (Accession 40173, 40174)., Extent: 4.25 cu. ft. (Box 6, 138-142)
  - Reading files, 2000 Aug 7-9 (Box 140, Folder 35)
  - Reading files, 2000 Aug 10-11 (Box 140, Folder 36)
  - Reading files, 2000 Aug 14-17 (Box 140, Folder 37)
  - Reading files, 2000 Aug 22-24 (Box 140, Folder 38)
  - Reading files, 2000 Aug 28-31 (Box 140, Folder 39)
  - Reading files, 2000 Sept 1 (Box 140, Folder 40)
  - Reading files, 2000 Sept 5-8 (Box 140, Folder 41)
  - Reading files, 2000 Sept 12-14 (Box 140, Folder 42)
  - Reading files, 2000 Sept 18-22 (Box 140, Folder 43)
  - Reading files, 2000 Sept 25-29 (Box 140, Folder 44)
  - Reading files, 2000 Oct 2-6 (Box 140, Folder 45)
  - Reading files, 2000 Oct 10-13 (Box 140, Folder 46)
  - Reading files, 2000 Oct 16-18 (Box 140, Folder 47)
  - Reading files, 2000 Oct 23-27 (Box 140, Folder 48)
  - Reading files, 2000 Oct 30-31 (Box 140, Folder 49)
  - Reading files, 2000 Nov 2-3 (Box 140, Folder 50)
  - Reading files, 2000 Nov 6-8 (Box 140, Folder 51)
  - Reading files, 2000 Nov 13-16 (Box 140, Folder 52)
  - Reading files, 2000 Nov 20-21 (Box 140, Folder 53)
  - Reading files, 2000 Nov 27-30 (Box 140, Folder 54)
  - Reading files, 2000 Dec 1 (Box 140, Folder 55)
  - Reading files, 2000 Dec 6-8 (Box 140, Folder 56)
  - Reading files, 2000 Dec 11-15 (Box 140, Folder 57)
  - Reading files, 2000 Dec 18-22 (Box 140, Folder 58)
  - Reading files, 2000 Dec 27 (Box 140, Folder 59)
  - Reading files, 2000 Dec 29 (Box 140, Folder 60)
  - Reading files, 2001 Jan 3-4 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Reading files, 2001 Jan 8-12 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Reading files, 2001 Jan 15-19 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Reading files, 2001 Jan 22-23 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Reading files, 2001 Jan 29-31 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Reading files, 2001 Feb 1 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Reading files, 2001 Feb 5-8 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Reading files, 2001 Feb 12-16 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Reading files, 2001 Feb 19-22 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Reading files, 2001 Feb 24-28 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Reading files, 2001 Mar 2 (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Reading files, 2001 Mar 5-9 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - Reading files, 2001 Mar 12-16 (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - Reading files, 2001 Mar 19-23 (Box 141, Folder 14)
  - Reading files, 2001 Mar 26-28 (Box 141, Folder 15)
  - Reading files, 2001 Apr 2-5 (Box 141, Folder 16)
  - Reading files, 2001 Apr 9-13 (Box 141, Folder 17)
  - Reading files, 2001 Apr 16 (Box 141, Folder 18)
  - Reading files, 2001 Apr 23-27, 30 (Box 141, Folder 19)
  - Reading files, 2001 May 1-4 (Box 141, Folder 20)
  - Reading files, 2001 May 16-17 (Box 141, Folder 21)
  - Reading files, 2001 May 21-23 (Box 141, Folder 22)
  - Reading files, 2001 May 29-31 (Box 141, Folder 23)
  - Reading files, 2001 June 1, 5-6 (Box 141, Folder 24)
  - Reading files, 2001 June 13-15 (Box 141, Folder 25)
  - Reading files, 2001 June 21-22, 26 (Box 141, Folder 26)
  - Reading files, 2001 July 3 (Box 141, Folder 27)
  - Reading files, 2001 July 12 (Box 141, Folder 28)
  - Reading files, 2001 July 18-19 (Box 141, Folder 29)
  - Reading files, 2001 July 23-26 (Box 141, Folder 30)
  - Reading files, 2001 July 31 (Box 141, Folder 31)
  - Reading files, 2001 Aug 1 (Box 141, Folder 32)
  - Reading files, 2001 Aug 6-10 (Box 141, Folder 33)
  - Reading files, 2001 Aug 14-17 (Box 141, Folder 34)
  - Reading files, 2001 Aug 21-24 (Box 141, Folder 35)
  - Reading files, 2001 Aug 27-30 (Box 141, Folder 36)
  - Reading files, 2001 Sept 4-6 (Box 141, Folder 37)
  - Reading files, 2001 Sept 10-14 (Box 141, Folder 38)
  - Reading files, 2001 Sept 17-20 (Box 141, Folder 39)
  - Reading files, 2001 Sept 24-27 (Box 141, Folder 40)
  - Reading files, 2001 Oct 1-5 (Box 141, Folder 41)
  - Reading files, 2001 Oct 15-18 (Box 141, Folder 42)
  - Reading files, 2001 Oct 23-25 (Box 141, Folder 43)
  - Reading files, 2001 Oct 29-31 (Box 141, Folder 44)
  - Reading files, 2001 Nov 2-27 (Box 141, Folder 45)
  - Reading files, 2001 Dec 3-28 (Box 141, Folder 46)
  - Reading files, 2002 Jan 2-4 (Box 141, Folder 47)
- Series XXI. Scheduling Office: Calendar, 1997 Nov-2002 Jan (Accession 39776)., Extent: 1 folder (Box 141)
  Calendar, 1997-2002, includes monthly calendar pages that include the Governor's appointments for each day.
  - Calendar, 1997 Nov-2002 Jan (Box 141, Folder 48)
- Series XXI. Chief of Staff: Correspondence and memoranda, 1998-2001 (Accession 39777)., Extent: .35 cu. ft. (Box 1)
  Correspondence and memoranda, 1998-2001, of Chief of Staff M. Boyd Marcus, Jr.
  - Correspondence and memoranda, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and memoranda, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and memoranda, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Series XXII. Executive Office: Executive Orders, 1998-2001 (Accession 39775)., Extent: .45 cu. ft. (Box 1)
  Executive Orders, 1998-2001, are arranged numerically. Executive orders No. 47 and No. 81 were not transferred with this collection. Hard copy of executive orders were printed from compact disk.
  Arranged numerically by executive order number.
  - Executive Orders No. 1-9, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Executive Orders No. 10-19, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Orders No. 20-29, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Executive Orders No. 30-39, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Executive Orders No. 40-49, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Executive Orders No. 50-59, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Executive Orders No. 60-69, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Executive Orders No. 70-79, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Executive Orders No. 80-85, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Executive Orders on compact disk, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)